[ Rumbling ]
[ Woman On Police Radio ]
Suspect describedas white male , approximately 30 .
Suspect about 5-11 " , medium build , brown dark pants .
Suspect number two about 6-1 , medium build , round glasses , dark clothes .
[ Leg Muscles Cracking ]
Be advised , suspects are armed and considered extremely dangerous . Use caution .
- [ Man ] Hey , Earl . - Yes , sir .
- What do ya know ? - Well ...
it 's a hot goddamn day .
I haven 't felt it a bit . Been inside with the air conditioner blasting all day long .
- Oh , is that right ? - That 's right .
[ Opens Bottle ]
Did you break for lunch or nothin ' ?
All by myself today . Ate my lunch out of the microwave .
Jesus H. Christ , Pete .
When you gonna learn that microwave food will kill you faster than a bullet ?
I mean , them damn burritos ain 't good for nothin ' but a hippie ... when he 's high on weed .
- Pull me down a bottle of that Jack , will ya ? - Yeah .
I think I 'm gonna get tanked tonight .
What 's the matter ?
[ Sighs ] Yep .
It 's been one long , goddamn , hot , miserable , shit-ass , fuckin ' day ...
every inch of the way .
First off , Nadine over at Blue Chip got sort of sick .
So she got that goddamn Mongoloid boy of hers workin ' the grill .
I mean , that fuckin ' idiot doesn 't know rat shit from Rice Krispies .
- [ Chuckles ] - They eat breakfast about 9 : 00 .
And I 'm puking ' up pigs in a blanket ...
like a sick , fuckin ' dog by 10 : 30 .
Isn 't there a law or something against retards serving food to the public ?
Well ... if there ain 't , there oughta be .
I mean , who in the hell knows what 's goin ' on in the mind of a goddamn Mongoloid ?
Nadine should 've hit that boy in the head and sold the fuckin ' milk .
You could sue the shit out ofher , you know that ?
That kid belongs under a circus tent , not flippin ' burgers .
- You could own that fuckin ' place . - Oh , shit , Pete .
What would I do with that grease pit ?
Besides , Nadine 's got a cross to bear .
I mean , taking care of that ... potato head .
I guess you heard about that shit up in Abilene ? Bank robbery ?
That 's all that 's been on the box all day .
They killed some people , didn 't they ?
Yeah . Killed four Rangers ,
three cops ,
one civilian .
Took a lady bank teller hostage with them .
Supposed to be headed for the border , which 'd bring ' em right my way .
If I get my hands on them crazy , sick , fuckin ' bastards , it 's payback time .
I mean- - Well , we 'll get ' em .
[ Sniffles ]
We 'll get ' em .
Oh , I don 't doubt it .
Well ...
I gotta drain my lizard .
- Mind if I useyour commode ? - [ Chuckles ]
- Knock yourself out . - Thank you .
You 're welcome .
- [ Moans ] - [ Cocks Gun ] You think I 'm fuckin playing ' with you , asshole ?
Do you want this little girl to die ? Or that little girl ? Or yourself ?
Or your bosom buddy with the badge ? Now , I don 't wanna do it .
But I will turn this place into the fucking Wild Bunch if I think you are fuckin ' with me .
- What do you want from me ? I did what you said . - You let him use the bathroom .
- No store does that . - He comes in here everyday and we bullshit .
- If I told him no , he 'd know something was up . - I want him out of here ...
in his car and down the road or you can change the name of this place ...
to " Benny 's World of Blood . "
[ Whispering ]
- You giving that pig signals ? - Are you kidding ? I didn 't do anything !
- He says you were scratching . - I wasn 't scratching ' !
- Are you callin ' him a liar ? - I 'm not callin ' him a liar , okay ?
I 'm simply saying ' if I was scratchin ' , I don 't remember scratching ' .
If I did scratch , it 's not signalling . It 's because I 'm fuckin ' scared shitless !
- [ Groans ] - Wait a minute . The guy 's in the bathroom .
Why don 't I just go back there , shoot him in the head , and we can get the hell outta here .
Don 't do that . Look . You asked me to act natural , and I acted natural .
Under the circumstances , I think I oughta get a fuckin ' Academy Award for how natural I did .
You asked me to get rid of him . I 'm doin ' my best ! [ Panting ]
Well , your best better get a hell of a lot fuckin ' better ,
- or you are gonna feel a hell of a lot fuckin ' worse . - [ Exhales ]
[ Toilet Flushes ]
Everybody , be cool . You ... be cool . [ Uncocks Gun ]
[ Gasps ]
Yep . Be back at it tomorrow .
Tonight I 'm gonna sit in front of that box and get higher than a Georgia pine .
- [ Chuckles ] - How much you want for that hooch , Pete ?
Oh , $ 6.50 .
- Jesus Christ . You buckin' for early retirement ? - Shit , yeah .
- [ Gunshot ] - [ Groans ]
- [ Girl Gasps ] - [ Robber # 1 ] Hey ! Hey !
- What the fuck is that about ? - He signalled the Ranger .
I didn 't ! Ya gotta believe me ! I didn 't !
When they were talking , he mouthed the words , " Help us . "
- You fuckin ' liar ! I didn 't say shit ! - Shut the hell up !
- [ Girl Gasps ] - Hey ! You stop it !
- What the fuck is your problem , goddamn it ? - Seth , he did it !
You were by the beer cooler with your back turned .
I was by the magazines . I could see his face !
And I saw him mouth the words , " Help us . "
Start the car .
- You believe me , don 't you ? - Yes . Shut up .
- And start the car . - You believe me ?
Start the car . You know that . Shut the fuck up and start the car .
- Wait a minute . - I believe you . Start the car !
- You 're not just saying that ? You do believe me ? - I believe you ! Let 's go !
- That means you believe . - Yes , I believe you !
You should , because I 'm right .
[ Screaming ]
- [ Robber # 2 Groaning ] - Richie !
Yeah ?
- You okay ? - He shot me in the fucking hand !
- I told you he said " Help us . " - I never said " Help us " !
Well , that doesn 't matter now , because you got about two fuckin ' seconds to live !
- Richie ? - Yeah ?
When I count to three , you shoot the bottles out from behind him .
Oh , yeah !
- One ... - Fuck !
- two ... - [ Gasping , Whimpering ]
three !
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Sighs ] - What did I tell you ? What did I say to you ?
I said , " Buy the road map and leave . "
- What the fuck am I supposed to do , Seth ? He recognized us . - He didn 't recognize shit .
Seth , I 'm telling you , the way he looked at us--you , especially--I knew he knew .
Low profile ! Do you understand the meaning of the words " low profile " ?
" Hey , Richie , how 's your hand ? " " It hurts like a fuckin ' son of a bitch ! Thanks for askin ' . "
Let me tell you what " low profile " is not . It is not taking girls hostage .
It is not shooting police . It is not setting fire to a building .
Bitch , bitch , bitch .
~ Hot airhangs like a deadman ~
~ From a white oak tree ~
~ People sitting 'on porches ~
~ Thinkin ' how things used to be ~
~ Dark night ~
~ It 's a dark night ~
~ It 's a dark night ~ ~
[ Engi ne Roaring ]
[ Spits ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Rings ]
[ Man On Radio ] ~ My wife left home about a week ago ~
- ~ She stole the kids and she took all my dough ~ - [ Bell Rings ]
Oh , screw it ! Goddamn you ! Goddamn you !
[ Muttering ] What the hell do you want ?
What do you think I want , you mean , old bastard ? I want a fuckin ' room .
Okay , all right .
~ She peed on the carpet She shot my horse ~
~ Now things are goin from better to bad to worse ~
Do they have cable ?
No .
- Do they have the X-rated channel ? - No .
- Do they have a water bed ? - Nope .
- What do they got ? - They have four walls and a roof and that 's all we need .
[ Shuts Engine Off ]
All right , pop the trunk . Let 's do this fast .
[ Whimpering ] Oh .
- Don 't say a word . - [ Gasps ]
You , plant yourself in that seat .
- What are you gonna do with me ? - I said " plant yourself . " Plants don 't talk .
Now , you wanna get on my goodside ? You sit still and you don 't make a peep .
- All right , how does this feel ? - How do you think- - It hurts like a son of a bitch .
- It 's wrapped too tight . Nice and easy . - Okay .
All right . Okay , I 'm gonna go get the money .
[ Panting ]
It 's 6 : 00 . What time 's it get dark around here ?
- About 8 : 00 . - Good . I 'm goin ' to the border , check things out .
I 'm gonna call Carlos . Try and arrange some sort of a rendezvous . I don 't know what .
Could you see if he could arrange a better deal than 30 % ?
It 's a standard deal . They 're not gonna change that for us .
- Did you even try and negotiate with them ? - Richie ,
these guys are not spic firecracker sales men from Tijuana .
They don 't even know the meaning of the word " barter . " You wanna stay in El Rey ,
you give them 30 % of your loot ; it 's scripture .
So it is written , so shall it be done . Yeah , I know , listen .
Hey , you want sanctuary , you gotta pay the price . The price is 30 % .
- All I 'm sayin ' , man- - - This conversation 's over .
Okay ?
We need to have a talk .
- What 's your name ? - Gloria .
Hello , Gloria . I 'm Seth . That 's my brother Richie . Let 's cut to the chase .
I 'm gonna ask you one question , and all I want is a yes or no answer .
Do you wanna live through this ?
- Yes . - Good .
Rule number one : No noise . No questions .
If you make a noise ,
Mr .. 44 makes a noise .
If you ask a question , Mr .. 44 answers it .
Now are you absolutely , positively clear about rule number one ?
- Yes . - Rule number two :
You do what we say when we say it .
If you don 't ... see rule number one .
Rule number three : Don 't you ever try and fucking run on us ,
'cause I got six little friends and they can all run faster than you can .
- [ Uncocks Gun ] - [ Whispers ] Open your eyes .
Gloria , you hang in there , you follow the rules ,
and you don 't fuck with us , and you 'll get out of this alive .
I give you my word . Okay ?
I 'll be back in a minute .
[ Door Opens , Closes ]
You wanna come over on the bed and watch TV with me ?
[ Men ] Hail !
Come on .
Come and see .
Take off your shoes .
[ Man ] You got about ... two more hours ...
until we get into El Paso ,
which is right next to the border .
- Then we 'll stop at a motel . - [ Boy ] Stop ?
- We 're not actually gonna stop at a motel , are we ? - Yeah , what for ?
We have a motor home . We don 't wanna stay in those roach-haven motels , do we ?
- [ Together ] We 're self-contained . - Okay , okay .
Maybe I was ... a little overzealous . But gimme a break . I just bought it .
- How come you wanna stop anyways , Dad ? - I 'm exhausted .
Exhausted ? Just lie in the back , Dad . I can drive us into Mexico .
- I just bet you would . Don 't even think about it . - [ Chuckles ]
Besides , I wanna have ...
just one night 's sleep in a honest to goodness bed .
The beds in the home are okay , but ...
they 're not like a real bed .
Excuse me . I have to use the restroom .
Oh , guess what ? When I called the machine to check the messages ,
um , one of them was from Bethel Baptist .
And Mr. Franklin said that ...
he wouldn 't permanently replace you until we came back .
- And he said that- - - That 's very nice of Ted .
But I 'll call him tomorrow and tell him not to bother waiting .
Daddy , I didn 't wanna talk about this ...
in front of Scott because he gets upset .
But I just wanna know ...
don 't you believe in God anymore ?
Not enough to be a pastor .
Look , I know this is hard on you kids .
After Jenny 's death , this is probably the last thing you need , but ...
my congregation needs spiritual leadership .
Well ... my faith is gone .
To answer your question , yes , I do believe in ... Jesus .
Yes , I do believe in God .
But do I love Them ?
No .
Well , it 's just that all our lives , you 've been a pastor .
And then ...
one day you 're just gonna wake up and say , " Fuck Him " ?
I didn 't say , " Fuck Him . "
Every person who ...
chooses the service of God as his life 's work has something in common .
I don 't care if you 're a preacher , a priest ,
a nun , a rabbi or a Buddhist monk .
Many , many times during your life you 'll look at your reflection in the mirror ...
and ask yourself ,
" Am I a fool ? "
I 'm not going through a lapse .
What I 've experienced is closer to awakening .
Daddy ?
What do you think Mom would say ?
Mama 's got nothin ' to say . She 's dead .
This bloody crime spree started just a week ago today .
The oldest of the two brothers , Seth Gecko ,
was serving time in Rollings , Kansas State Penitentiary ...
for his part in the 1988 Scott City bank robbery ...
in which two law enforcement officers lost their lives .
It was while at the courthouse that this man , his younger brother , Richard Gecko ,
a known armed robber and sex offender pulled off a daring daylight escape ,
resulting in the death of four Wichita law enforcement officers , and this woman ,
Heidi Vogel , sixth grade teacher , who was run over by the Geckos ...
during a high-speed pursuit through downtown Wichita .
And earlier today , during a daylight liquor store robbery in Big Springs ,
the Gecko brothers killed another Texas Ranger ,
Earl McGraw , and liquor store clerk , Pete Bottoms .
That changes the death toll to 16 ;
five Texas Rangers , eight police officers , three civilians .
And one hostage , bank teller and mother off our , Gloria Hill .
For the time being , we 're very confident that we 'll apprehend these fugitives within 48 hours .
The Bureau , local law enforcement and the Texas Rangers ...
have all joined in forming a dragnet to snare Seth and Richard Gecko .
Is it safe to assume that because of the death count involved ...
and the loss of life of law enforcement officers ,
that the Bureau , the Rangers and the police force are taking this manhunt personally ?
I would say that 's a very safe assumption .
[ Door Opening ]
- Shit , I was really worried . Where the fuck you been , man ? - Sightseeing .
- What 'd you see ? - The cops .
- Did you see the border ? - Yes , I saw the border .
- What 'd the TV say ? - They 're gonna apprehend us in about 48 hours .
I gotta figure out a way to get us across this goddamn border .
The longer we stay here , our lives ain 't worth shit . Here you go .
We gotta get our asses into Mexico tonight .
Then Carlos is gonna meet us at the rendezvous tomorrow morning .
He and his boys , all of them are gonna escort us into El Rey .
And- -
- Where 's the woman ? - What ?
What do you mean , what ? The woman . The fuckin ' hostage .
Richard , where is she ?
She 's in there .
- What the fuck is she doin ' in there ? - Seth , wait a minute .
Seth .
Richard , what 's wrong with you ?
- Before you flip out , okay , let me just explain what happened . - Ex--Explain to me .
I need an explanation . What is the matter with you ?
There 's nothing wrong with me , brother . That woman tried to escape and I did what I had to .
No , the woman wouldn 't have said shit if she had a mouth full of it .
Wrong , wrong , wrong .
- Yeah . - After you left ,
- she became a completely different person . - Yeah .
Is it me ? Is it my fault ?
- It 's not your fault . - Is this my fault ?
- No , it 's her fault . It 's not your fault . - Is this my fault ?
Do you think that this is what I am ?
- I don 't . - This is not me . I am a professional fucking thief .
I don 't kill people that I don 't have to and I don 't fucking rape women .
What you are doing- - What you are fucking doing- -
What you are doing is not how it 's done . Do you understand that ? Do you ?
Just say , " Fucking yes . " Say , " Yes , Seth , I understand . "
- Yes , Seth , I understand . - Say it . Say , " Yes , Seth , I fucking understand ! "
I understand , Seth . I fucking understand .
We 'll get to Mexico , and it 's gonna be sweet rosemary and a hundred proof liquor ...
[ Sighs ] and rice and beans and none of this shit 's gonna matter .
I can 't believe he 's stoppin ' here . This place is totally cruddy .
- [ Door Closes ] - Dad , why are we stoppin ' here ?
There 's nothin ' wrong with this ... place .
- [ Engine Starts ] - It 's a flophouse .
It 's not a flophouse .
It 's basic and it 's simple .
That doesn 't make it a flophouse .
All right . Well , if it doesn 't have a pool ,
then we 're goin ' someplace else .
It has a bed .
That 's all I care about .
Well , other places have beds , too ,
and they also have ... a gym-
[ Brakes Screeching ] - [ Gasps ]
[ Scott ] Geez , what is this guy 's problem ?
No idea .
Creepy guy .
[ Knocking ]
~ [ Guitar ]
- [ Knocking ] - What ?
- [ Richard ] Yes , I 'm your neighbor from , uh , room 11 . - [ Sighs ]
And I hate to disturb you , but I 'd like to ask a favor .
[ Moaning ]
I hope none of this is disturbing ' you .
[ Exhales ]
Hi . Uh , I 'm from room 11 .
And me and my lady friend need some ice and we don 't seem to have an ice bucket .
If it 's not too much trouble , could I possibly borrow yours ? I 'll bring it right back .
[ Sighs ] Sure .
Thank you .
[ Gun Cocks ]
What is this ?
- [ Groans ] - It 's called a punch .
Lose the guitar .
- [ Gun Cocks ] - What 's your name ?
- Jacob . - Jacob , get up . Get on the bed .
- If you make a wrong move , I will shoot you in the face . - [ Richard ] Open your mouth .
Wide !
Let 's go . Let 's move the Jap over here too . Let 's go .
So what 's the story with you two ? You a couple offags ?
- He 's my son . - How 's that happen ? You don 't look Japanese .
Neither does he . He looks Chinese .
Oh , ooh , well excuse me all to hell .
- What 's this about , money ? - It 's about money , all right , but not yours .
My brother and I , we 're in a little hot water and we need your assistance .
- [ Gasps ] - Stop !
Wha--What 's , um , goin ' on ?
We 're having a bikini contest , and you just won .
It 's okay , honey . Everything 's gonna be all right .
Just listen to your daddy , sugar , and you don 't do anything stupid .
You two , Simon says sit the fuck down .
Sit down .
Now ... where are the keys to the motor home ?
- On the dresser . - Good . All right ,
Richie , you take these keys , you start this big bastard up and drive it up front .
Richie , would you do me a favor and eat my pussy for me ? Please ?
- Uh ... sure . - Richie , hey !
Not when you get around to it . Now .
[ Groans ]
You , Gidget , go in the bathroom and put on some clothes .
You got three minutes . One second longer , I shoot your father in the face .
- Do you understand what I just said ? - Yes .
- Do you believe me ? - Yes .
You damn well better . Go .
Look , if you want the motor home ,
just take it and get out .
It 's not gonna be that easy , Pops . We 're gonna go on a little ride .
Not a chance .
- Come again ? - If you 're takin ' people , take me .
But my kids aren 't going anywhere with you .
Sorry , Pops . I need everybody .
My children are not goin with you , and that 's that .
That 's not fucking that . This is fucking this .
Dad .
You sit down . Sit down .
You , go sit over there . Go sit over there , now . Move it .
Sit down .
Now , I don 't have time to fuck around , so I 'm gonna make this simple .
You take your kids and you get in that motor home ...
or I will execute all three of you right now .
So , what 's it gonna be ?
Yes or no answer .
Yes .
Hey , your old man 's all right . He just saved your life .
Time 's up , princess . Here we go .
Okay , ramblers , let 's get rambling .
Excuse me .
What ?
- Where are you takin ' us ? - Mexico .
What 's in Mexico ?
Mexicans .
- Richie ? - Yeah ?
Put in your bit .
[ Rattling ]
I grind my teeth .
~ Dengue woman ~
What are their names ?
- Scott and Kate . - Scott and Kate .
Who 's this ?
- My wife . - Where is the little lady ?
- In heaven . - She dead ?
Yes , she is .
How 'd she die ?
Auto wreck .
Come on , Jacob , gimme some more details . How 'd it happen ? Some fucking drunk kill her ?
No . It was a rainy night .
The brakes on the car weren 't great .
She had to stop suddenly .
She slid on the road . She crashed . She died .
- She died right away ? - Not quite .
She was trapped in the wreck for about ... six hours ...
before she passed on .
Yep . Those acts of God really stick it in and break it off , don 't they ?
Yes , they do .
Is that real ?
- Yes . - I 've seen one of these things before .
A friend of mine had himself ordained a minister of his own religion .
Some way to fuck the I.R.S. Is that what you 're doing , or are you the real McCoy ?
The real McCoy .
- You 're a preacher ? - [ Inhales Deeply ] I was a minister .
" Was " as in not anymore ?
- Yes . - Why 'd you quit ?
I think I 've gotten about ...
as up close and personal with you as I 'm gonna get .
Let 's just keep this friendly , okay , Pops ? Let 's not get too sensitive .
You 're right . Enough with the gettin ' - to-know-you shit . All right .
I don 't give a rat 's ass about you or your fuckin ' family .
You can all live forever , or you can die this second .
And I don 't give a shit which .
The only things that I care about are me ,
that son of a bitch back there in the back and the money .
So you help us get across the border without incident ,
you stay with us through the night without trying anything funny ,
without trying to escape ,
and in the morning I 'm gonna let you guys go , all of you .
How do I know you 'll keep your word ? You have to convince me you 're tellin ' the truth .
Look , dick-head , the only thing that you have to be convinced about ...
is the fact that you are stuck in a situation with a couple of real mean motor scooters .
I don 't want to have to worry about you all fuckin 'night .
I don 't think you wanna be worrying about my brother 's intentions ...
towards your daughter all night , either .
- Did you notice the way he was looking at her ? - Yes .
- You didn 't like it , did you ? - No , I didn 't .
I didn 't think so . You get us into Mexico ,
and you don 't try to escape , and your daughter will be safe .
And in the morning I will let you go . I give you my word , Jacob .
If he touches her , I 'll kill him !
Fair enough . You break your word , I 'll kill all of ya .
~ You got me all crazy ~
~ I can 't get outta bed ~
~ Bones are achin ' ~
~ Backed up in myhead ~
~ Dengue woman ~
~ Stay away from me ~
~ You got your aches andpains ~
~ O-o-over me ~ ~
Did you mean what you said back there in the room ?
What ?
In the room ?
Did you mean what you said back there , or were just foolin ' around ?
Because if you really want me to do that for you , I will . I 'd be happy to .
- Do what ? - What you said back there in the room ?
What did I say ?
- You asked me if I would eat- - - [ Seth ] Richie .
- What ? - I told you to watch those kids . Not to talk to them .
You don 't have nothin ' to say to one another , so let 's just cut the chatter .
We 'll talk later . Okay ?
[ People Chattering ]
[ Man On Police Radio ]
All right , everybody , it 's show time .
Richie , you take Kate into the bathroom . Scott , get up here with your dad . Let 's go .
Now , what are you gonna say ?
I don 't have the slightest idea .
Just keep thinking about the gun next to Kate 's head .
Get in .
[ Chattering Continues ]
- [ Panting ] - This isn 't gonna work , Seth .
Shut up . It 's gonna work just fine .
[ Whispering ] What are you gonna do ?
I 'm gonna try and get us across the border .
Dad , you have to tell them they 're back there .
Have you forgotten about your sister ?
I want to go on record right now as saying that this is a very bad idea .
Duly noted . Now shut up .
Oh , my God . Look over here . Step right over there .
They 're gonna kill us , Dad . They 're gonna get us across the border ,
take us out in the desert , then they 're gonna fuckin ' shoot us .
If they get over the border , they 're gonna let us go .
No , they won 't . Dad , come on . I watch those reality shows . They never let anybody go .
Any cop 'll tell you , in a situation like this , you get a chance , you go for it .
It may not seem like it , but I know exactly what I 'm doing . Trust me .
I can 't do that , Dad .
- If you don 't tell the cops , I will . - Now listen to me !
You ain 't gonna do a goddamn thing ! You hear me ?
- I 'm runnin ' the show ! I make the decisions ! - He is runnin ' the show- -
- I 'm runnin ' the show ! - Dad !
Shh . I make the plays .
You back the plays I make .
I need your cover .
Cover me .
How many with you ?
- Just my son and I. - [ Thumping ]
What 's your purpose in Mexico ?
Vacation . I 'm takin ' him to see his first bull fight .
They 're gonna search the van .
As long as you don 't act like a fuckin ' nut , we 're gonna be fine .
- What the hell 's that supposed to mean ? - What ?
- You just called me a fuckin ' nut . - No , I didn 't .
Yes , you did . You said , " As long as I don 't act like a fucking nut . "
- Implying that I 've been acting like a fucking nut . - Take a pill .
- I just meant be cool . - Yeah , you meant that , but you meant the other too .
[ Sighs ] This is not the time , Richie .
Hey , fuck those spic pigs , man ! You called me a " fucking nut . "
- Now , where I come from , that stops the train in its tracks . - Keep your fucking voice down .
- [ Banging ] - What ?
- What was that ? - Hmm ?
Oh ! That was just , just my daughter in the bathroom .
I thought you said it was just you and your son ?
Um ... I meant me and my son and my daughter .
Open up . I 'm comin ' aboard .
What was the nuttiest thing I did , Seth ? I 'm curious . Tell me . What was it ?
- This is not the time , Richie . - I know .
Was it possibly when your ass was rotting in jail and I broke it out ?
- [ Chuckles ] - That was nutty , huh ? Not to mention stupid .
[ Sighs ]
Thanks .
[ Panting ]
- [ Kate ] I 'm in the bathroom . - Open up . It 's Border Patrol .
It 's open .
[ Gasps ]
Do you mind ? Shut the fuckin ' door , please !
Excuse me .
Goddamn , that was intense !
Oh , baby , we did it . We 're in Mexico .
We 're fuckin ' in Mexico , you little piece of fuckin ' shit !
Come on ! Kate , get out here .
All right , listen up . Everybody , listen .
Now I know that I put you all through hell , and I know that I have been one rough pecker .
But from here on out , you guys are all in my cool book .
Scotty , I want you to help me with Richie . Lay him down on the couch over there.Jacob.
You 're gonna keep driving down this street until you come to another street called Digallo .
When you get to Digallo , you 're gonna turn this big bastard left ,
and you 're gonna go down a couple of miles until you see a bar called the Titty Twister .
- From what I understand , you cannot miss it . - Then ?
And then you stop because that 's where we 're goin ' .
~ [ Spanish ]
Don 't make a career out of this , okay ?
- Come on , hey . - [ Sighs ]
Hey , you okay ?
[ Groans ] Yeah , I think so . What happened ?
- I don 't know . You just passed out . - I did ?
Mm-hmm . You said something about your hand hurtin ' ,
- and then you just hit the ground like a sack of potatoes . [ Chuckles ] - Really ?
Head hit the toilet . You scared the shit out of me .
You sure you 're okay ?
Yeah . I , I think so . I 'm just a little fucked up .
Well , let me tell you something that 's gonna clear your head right up .
- What ? - We are officially Mexicans .
[ Chuckling ] We 're in Mexico , buddy .
- We are ? - Yeah . We 're heading down to the rendezvous right now .
We 're gonna pound booze , wait for Carlos .
When he gets there , he 's gonna take us down to El Rey .
And then you and I , my brother , we 're gonna kick fuckin ' back .
- How do you like them apples ? - Far out .
- [ Chuckling ] - [ Groaning ] Where 's my glasses ?
Oh , uh--Yeah , they , uh- - they broke when you fell .
- Fuck , Seth , these are my only pair ! - Don 't worry about it .
- We 'll get you another pair . - Of course I 'm gonna worry about it . I can 't see !
I 'll take care of it when we get to El Rey .
Yeah , like some Mexican hole in the wall 's gonna have my prescription .
It 's not a big deal until you make it a big deal . Now , I was in a very good mood .
So stop bringing me down with this bullshit !
[ Scoffs ]
- I can 't wear this shit . - Hey , guys .
We 're here .
~ [ Rock ]
[ Man Laughing ]
[ Shouting ] Pussy !
[ Chuckling ]
All right , pussy , pussy , pussy !
Come on in , pussy lovers .
Here at the Titty Twister , we 're slashing ' pussy in half .
Give us an offer on our best selection of pussy . This is a pussy blowout !
All right , we got white pussy , black pussy , Spanish pussy , yellow pussy .
We got hot pussy , cold pussy .
We got wet pussy . We got smelly pussy .
We got hairy pussy , bloody pussy . We got snapping ' pussy .
We got silk pussy , velvet pussy , " Nalgahyde " pussy .
We even got horse pussy , dog pussy , chicken pussy .
Come on , you want pussy . Come on in , pussy lovers .
If we don 't got it , you don 't want it . Come on in , pussy lovers .
Okay , troops , it 's the homestretch . Here 's the deal .
This place closes at dawn . Carlos is gonna meet us here sometime before dawn .
Now , we are gonna go in there , we 're gonna take a seat , we 're gonna have a bunch of drinks .
And we 're gonna wait for Carlos .
Let me just say something . I 'm very happy about where we 're at .
We got a real nice I-don 't - fuck-with-you , you-don 't-fuck - with-me attitude goin ' on .
So if everybody just keeps playin ' it cool--I 'm talkin ' to you , too , Richie- -
then everybody 's gonna get what they want .
Okay , hard drinkers , let 's drink hard . I 'm buyin ' . Come on .
Here we go .
Out of the stew pot and into the fire .
Attention , pussy shoppers ! Take advantage of our penny pussy sale .
If you buy one piece of pussy at the regular price ,
you will get another piece of pussy of equal or lesser value for only a penny .
Try and beat pussy for a penny .
If you can find cheaper pussy anywhere ... fuck it !
[ Laughing ]
Hey , what do we have approaching here ?
A new flavor : apple pie pussy . [ Chuckles ]
Hey , not so fast , slick .
- Step aside , asshole . - [ Wrist Cracking ]
Son of a- - [ Groaning ]
Now , is my shit together or is my shit together ?
Here we go .
- Hi ! How ya doin ' ? Enjoying it ? I hope so ! - [ Groaning ]
Now ... this is my kind of place .
~ [ Rock ]
[ Bottle Shattering ]
~ [ Singing In Spanish ]
I could become a regular .
[ Punch Landing ]
[ Bottle Smashing ]
~ [ Continues Singing In Spanish ]
Whiskey !
- You can 't come in here . - What do you mean ?
It 's a private bar . You 're not welcome .
Are you tellin ' me that I 'm not good enough to drink here ?
This baris for bikers and truckers only .
You , get out !
Ande , pendejo !
- Take your hand off of me . - I 'm gonna count to three- -
- No , I 'm gonna count to three . - One- -
- Two- - - Now , wait a minute . There is no reason to get ugly .
There is just a misunderstanding going on here .
You said this bar is for truckers and bikers ?
Well , I 'm a truck driver .
If you look outside your door in your parking lot , you 'll see a big recreational vehicle .
That 's mine . In order to drive that legally , you need a Class Two driver 's license .
This bar is for truck drivers ?
I am a truck driver .
These are my friends .
[ Screaming ]
Welcome to the Titty Twister .
- Bottle of whiskey and five glasses . - Coming right up .
~ [ Continues Singing In Spanish ]
[ Screaming ]
~ [ Trilling ]
- You serve food here , Jose ? - Best in Mexico .
I kind of doubt that .
We 're gonna go over here . You send a waitress over to take our order . Okay ?
- [ Bottle Smashes ] - ~ [ Stops ]
~ [ Starts ]
[ Whip Snaps ]
~ Mary had a little lamb ~
~ His fleece was black as coal , yeah ~
Any time you want a lap dance with that girl , kid , just let me know , all right ?
It 's on me .
Pass .
Is it against your religion ?
No . I do drink . I 'm just not drinkin ' now .
- Fair enough . More for me . Scott , how ' bout you ? - No .
- Kate , how ' bout you ? - No , I can 't . I 'm not 21 yet .
That means yes .
Post time , Kate !
Here we go . You slam it down . You knock the glass down on the table , all right ?
One , two , three !
- [ Coughing ] - Atta girl , Kate .
- Scotty , are you ready ? Here we go . You ready for one ? - Okay .
- No , he won 't . - Yes , he will , because I 'm not drinkin ' by myself .
Kate , round two . You ready ?
- Here we go . - Yes , I 'll have another one . Thank you .
On three . One , two , three .
[ Coughing ]
Why are you so agitated ?
I 'm still stewing ' about that ape laying ' his hand on me .
- What are you gonna do ? - I 'm gonna sit here and I 'm gonna finish this bottle .
And when I am finished , I 'm gonna take this bottle and I 'm gonna bust it ...
over his melon fucking head !
Before we stepped in here , you told all of us to be cool . So , that means you too .
I never said do what I do . I said do what I say .
~ Expressyourself ~
Are you such a fucking loser ...
you can 't tell when you 've won ?
- What 'd you call me ? - Nothing .
I didn 't make a statement . I asked a question .
- Would you like me to ask it again ? - Mm-hmm .
Are you such a loser you can 't tell when you 've won ?
The entire state of Texas ...
along with the F.B.I. are lookin ' for you .
Did they find you ? No , they couldn 't .
You 've won , Seth .
Enjoy it .
- Jacob . - ~ [ Stops ]
I want you to have a drink with me . I insist .
To your family .
To yours .
And now , for your viewing pleasure ,
the Mistress of the Macabre ,
the Epitome of Evil , the most sinister woman to ever dance on the face of this earth .
- [ Man ] Bite this ! - Lowly dog !
Bow your head . Kneel and worship ...
at the feet of Santanico Pandemonium !
[ Man ] Ooow !
[ Man Gasps ]
[ Hissing ]
~ Watching her ~
~ Strolling in the night ~
~ So right ~
~ Wondering why ~
~ It 's only after dark ~
~ Feel her eyes ~
~ The distant firelight ~
~ Burns bright ~
~ Wondering why ~
~ It 's only after dark ~
[ Continues Hissing ]
~ Find myself ~
~ In the room ~
~ Feel the fever ofmy doom ~
~ Falling for her through the floor ~
~ I 'm knocking on the devil 's door ~
~ Yeah ~
~ Burning my internal flame ~
~ Now that they know her secret name ~
~ You can tell whose heaven will go ~
~ But she 'll be back and through the gate ~
~ Yeah ~
~ [ Stops ]
[ Cheering ]
That 's what I call a fuckin ' show !
[ Seth ] Wow !
- Come here ! - [ Cheering Continues ]
- That guy ! It 's the puta over there ! - Richie , get back on the clock .
- How many ? - Three .
Which one ?
This piece of shit here , man , broke my finger and my nose !
And this faggot kicked me in the ribs while I was down !
- Up ! - [ Cocks Gun ] Fuck you , bogeyman !
- [ Grunting ] - [ Screaming ]
Fuck ! [ Groaning ] Fuck !
- Fuck you ! - [ Groaning ]
All right ! Everybody be cool , or you 'll be just as dead as these fucks !
How 's your hand ? Let me see it .
- Shit . - [ Panting ]
[ Chuckling ]
- You think that was funny ? - [ Chuckles ]
[ Groans ]
Sit down !
[ Hissing , Heavy Sigh ]
[ Skin Stretching ]
- Richie , look out ! - Motherfuckin ' shit ! Get the fuck off !
- Hey ! Hey ! - Get her off me !
- [ Gun Clicking ] - What the fuck are you doing ? Shoot her !
- [ Biting Neck ] - [ Screaming ]
- I 'm comin ' , buddy ! - [ Moaning ]
- [ Groaning ] - Richie . Richie . Rich .
- [ Panting ] - Richie .
Fucking bitch !
- Richie . - [ Breathing Stops ]
Hey .
[ Panting ]
[ Roaring ]
- [ Screaming ] - [ Roaring Loudly ]
What the fuck ?
[ Crowd Screaming ]
Dinner ... [ Voice Distorting ] is served .
[ Maniacal Laughter , Biting ]
- [ Hissing ] - What the fuck ?
- Fuck ! Get off me- - - [ Skin Tearing ]
Come on ! Come on , you !
Jacob !
[ Man Shouting ] Oh , no ! Look out ! Look out !
[ Growling ]
- [ Screams ] - You know what everybody says about me , huh ?
- I suck ! [ Laughing ] - [ Screams ]
- [ Growls ] - [ Groans ]
- [ Groans ] - [ Screams ]
- [ Moaning ] - [ Body Seething ]
- [ Screaming ] - [ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
[ Panting , Gasps ]
- [ Body Being Impaled ] - Eeew .
[ Crowd Shouting ]
Let 's see if you taste as good as your brother .
- [ Cocks Gun ] - Fuck you !
[ Gun Clicking ]
- [ Grunts ] - [ Screaming , Groans ]
[ Vampire Roaring ]
[ Grunts ] Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
- [ Grunts ] - [ Screaming ]
- [ Screams ] - [ Vampire Groans ]
[ Growling ]
Oh , shit !
- Huh ? - [ Whip Snapping ]
[ Growls , Roaring ]
- Gimme that ! - [ Groans ]
- [ Moaning ] - Hmph .
[ Screaming Intensifies ]
~ [ Stops ]
- [ Groans ] - I 'm not gonna drain you completely .
You 'll be my slave .
Because I don 't think you 're worthy of human blood . You feed on the blood of stray dogs .
- [ Groans ] - You 'll be my foot stool .
And at my command , you 'll lick the dog shit from my boot heel .
- Ooh ? - Since you 'll be my dog ,
your new name will be ... Spud .
Welcome ... to slavery .
No , thanks . I already had a wife .
[ Flesh Sizzling ]
[ Roaring ]
- [ Neck Cracks ] - We might be in trouble .
- [ Growling ] - Yo , monkey man .
Anything you got to say to them ,
say to me first .
[ Roaring ]
This ! [ Karate Cries ]
[ Beating ]
[ Growling ]
That 's enough .
[ Heart Squeaking ]
[ Growls ]
[ Low Growling ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Body Hits Floor ]
- [ Sighs ] - [ Kate Panting ]
Ain 't they supposed to burn up or something ?
Oh ... fuck .
[ Panting , Grunts ]
Now let 's kill that fuckin ' band !
I can do that .
Fuck you , everybody . Good night !
Fuckers .
Hey , buddy .
I 'm sorry I fucked things up , Richie .
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ] You would 've liked it in El Rey . You would 've .
You would 've found peace .
I love you , Richie .
[ Demonic Voice ] I love you too , Seth . [ Roaring ]
[ Groans ]
- [ Cocks Gun ] - You touch my brother with that stake , biker ,
and vampires aren 't gonna have to suck your blood ; they 'll be able to lick it off the floor .
- He 's not your brother anymore . - That 's a matter of opinion , and I don 't give a fuck about yours .
Don 't be a fool ! He 'll kill us all .
- Shut up ! - Yeah , shut up !
Let 's go . Move , move .
[ Growls ]
Hold him down .
Richie .
Here is the peace in death that I could not give you in life .
- [ Screams ] - [ Continues Pounding ]
[ Grunts , Groans ]
[ Groans ]
- Fuck ! - [ Kicks Arm ]
[ Bottles Rattling ]
Seth ... are you okay ?
I 'm peachy , Kate . The world is my oyster .
Except for the fact that I just- -
I just rammed a wooden stake into my brother 's chest ...
because he turned into a vampire .
Even though I don 't believe in vampires .
Aside from that unfortunate business ,
everything is hunky-dory .
- I 'm really , really sorry . - Bullshit ! Bullshit !
If it were up to you , if you had half a chance , you would feed us to those fucks .
Then why didn 't I ?
I 'm sorry you lost your brother . I 'm sorry he 's dead . I 'm sorry everybody 's dead .
But if we 're gonna get out of this , we need you clean and sober and thinking .
Not drunk .
- [ Whirring ] - What is that ?
Don 't know . First I thought it was just ... birds .
It 's bats .
[ Screeching ]
Gimme a hand .
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams , Panting ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Low Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Roaring ] - No !
Hey !
Whoa .
[ Roaring ]
You 're dead ! Oh-
[ Bottles Smashing ] - Come on !
We 'll take care of this mess . You go stake the rest of those ugly fucks .
Way ahead of you .
- Watch your step . What 's your name , girlie ? - Kate . What 's yours ?
- Sex Machine . Pleased to meet you , Kate . - You too .
[ Sighs , Panting ]
[ Screeching ]
- [ Vampire Screaming ] - [ Sighing ]
- [ Roaring ] - [ Gasps ]
- [ Ripping Flesh ] - [ Sighs ]
[ Grunts , Sighs ]
- Is everybody okay ? - Yeah . I 'm okay .
[ Jacob ] Does anybody know what 's going on here ?
I know what 's goin ' on . We 've got a bunch of vampires out there ...
trying to get in here and suck our fucking blood , and that 's it , plain and simple .
And I don 't wanna hear anything about " I don 't believe in vampires . "
Because I don 't fucking believe in vampires , but I believe in my own two eyes .
And what I saw is fucking vampires .
Now , do we all agree that what we are dealing with is vampires ?
- [ Kate ] Yes . - You , too , preacher ?
I don 't believe in vampires , but I believe in what I saw .
Good for you . Now that we agree we 're dealing with vampires , what do we know about vampires ?
- Crosses hurt vampires . Do we have a cross ? - In the motor home .
- In other words , no . - [ Scott ] Wait a second.Just look around .
We got crosses all over the place . All you gotta do is put two sticks together ,
- and you got a cross . - Yeah , he 's right . Peter Cushing does that all the time .
Okay , I 'll buy that . So , we got crosses covered . What else ?
Wooden stakes in the heart have been working pretty good so far .
And garlic , sunlight , holywater . I 'm not sure .
- Doesn 't silver have something to do with vampires ? - That 's werewolves .
I know silver bullets are werewolves . I 'm sure silver has something to do with vampires .
Well , does anybody have any silver ?
Okay . Then , who cares ?
Has anybody here read a real book about vampires ,
or are we just rememberin' what some movie said ?
- I mean , a real book . - You mean like a Time-Life book ?
I take it the answer 's no . Okay , then .
What do we know about these vampires ?
We know they got superhuman strength , but we can hurt ' em .
- Yeah . - [ Sex Machine ] Another thing , though .
If you 're gonna drive a chair leg through a human , you better be one strong son of a bitch .
I mean , the human body is ... one rough , tough machine . [ Chuckles ]
But these vamps- - these vamps , they 're- - they have soft bodies .
The texture of their skin is soft . And they 're mushier .
You can push shit right through them .
Conceivably , if you hit one hard enough , take their head right off .
[ Seth ] Actually , our best weapon against these satanic cocksuckers ...
is this man .
He 's a preacher . As far as God 's concerned ,
we might as well all be a piece of shit , but he 's one of the boys .
Only one problem : his faith isn 't what it used to be . [ Groans ]
I 've had enough of your taunts .
I 'm not taunting you , Jacob . We need you .
A faithless preacher ...
doesn 't mean shit to us .
A servant of God can take a cross and shove it up these monsters ' asses .
A servant of God can bless the tap water and make it a weapon .
Jacob ...
I know why you lost your faith .
How could holiness exist if your wife can be taken away from you and your children ?
Now , I 've always said that God can kiss my ass ,
but I just changed my lifetime tune about 30 minutes ago .
'Cause I know that whatever is out there trying to get in ...
is pure evil straight from hell .
And if there is a hell , and those sons of bitches are from it ,
then there has got to be a heaven , Jacob ; there 's gotta be !
So , which are you ?
Are you a faithless preacher , or are you a mean motherfuckin ' servant of God ?
I 'm a mean- - [ Moaning ]
servant of God .
[ Bats Hovering ]
I don 't know if I can take much more of that noise .
Sure you can .
You can take it because you got no choice .
How 'd you like to spend 24 hours of it lying in some muddy ditch ,
with nothing but the rotten corpses of your friends to keep you company ?
- What are you talkin ' about ? - [ Ignites Match ]
I was in ' Nam ...
back in ' 72 .
I was trapped behind enemy lines ...
with my entire squad dead .
They thought they had killed everyone .
Except for me , they was right .
But it wasn 't for their lack of tryin ' .
A grenade ...
blew up right beside me .
That 's why I 'm so pretty .
And they start pushin all them bodies in on top of me .
And all I could do was lay there .
Play possum .
Listen to the enemy joke , laugh , hour ...
after hour after hour .
- So I finally- - [ Continues Speaking ] - [ Female Vampires ] Kill them .
Kill them . Kill them all .
Sex Machine .
Kill them .
So I finally climbed out of this hole ...
and I sneaked up on the enemy while he was sleeping .
And I killed one , two , three , four , five- -
I came to my senses ,
and I realized ... I had killed an entire V.C. squad .
Single-handed .
There was ... blood ...
and chunks of ... yellow flesh ... clinging to my bayonet .
To this day , I don 't remember-
[ Roaring ] - [ Screaming ]
Get him off of me ! Get off of me !
Please ! Get him off !
[ Screaming ]
- No ! - [ Screaming ]
[ Kate ] Dad !
[ Screaming ]
He fuckin 'bit me . He fuckin 'bit me !
- What are you gonna do about it ? - Come on , Sex Machine .
[ Low Growling ]
Oh ... shit !
Get up ! Get up ! Up ! Come on !
[ Grunting ]
- Go ! Fuck ! - [ Screeching ]
- Wait . We have to go back for my father . - Your dad 's dead , Kate .
[ Vampire Growling ]
[ Growling Getting Closer ]
The people ... who walk ...
in the darkness ...
have seen the light !
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Jacob ] Open the door !
Open the door !
Go ! Go !
Oh , Daddy !
[ Seth ] Jacob , are you bit ?
Yeah .
Motherfuck . Motherfuckin ' vampires !
I 'm gonna kill every last one of you godless , fuckin ' pieces of shit !
You bet you are , and I 'm gonna help you do it . But we ain 't got much time .
- You 're gonna be okay , aren 't you ? - No , I 'm not .
I 've been bit . In fact , I 'm already dead .
Now ...
I 'd say in the next 20 or 30 minutes our friends outside will bust in this door .
And I 'll probably turn into a vampire within the hour .
Now , you have two choices . You can wait for me to turn , then deal with me .
Or we can kick open that door , and the four of us ...
can go at ' em , hit ' em with everything we have .
But if we 're gonna go at ' em , we gotta go at ' em now .
What 's this stuff ?
My guess is this little dive ...
has been feeding on bikers and truckers for a long time .
This is probably the shipments they stole off the trucks .
I say , let 's tear this place apart for weapons .
So when they burst through , we 'll make ' em wish they never did .
I don 't care about livin ' or dyin ' anymore . I just wanna send as many of these devils ...
- back to hell as I can . - Amen .
[ Low Growling ]
Loving God , bless this water ...
and give us Your protection and strength in this , our darkest hour . Amen .
Before we go any further , I need you three to promise me somethin ' .
I 'll fight with you ' til the bitter end , but when I turn into one of them ,
I won 't be Jacob anymore .
I 'll be a lapdog of Satan .
I want you three to promise you 'll take me down , no different from the rest .
I promise , Jacob .
Kate ? Scott ?
I promise .
- Scott ? - Yeah , I promise .
Why don 't I believe you ?
I 'm gonna ask you two again .
Then I want you to swear to God ...
that you 'll kill me !
If you don 't , I 'm gonna just kill myself right now .
Now , since you need me , I think you better swear !
Kate , do you swear to God that when I become one of the undead ,
you 'll kill me ?
Kate !
We don 't have much time , so I 'm only giving you to the count of five . One , two ,
three , four- -
Okay , all right ! I promise I 'll do it !
Good girl . Now , Scott ,
we have even less time , so I 'm giving you the count of three .
- One- - - You don 't believe in suicide .
It 's not suicide ... if you 're already dead . Two- -
Okay ! Okay .
- I 'll kill you when you change . I swear to God in Jesus Christ 's name . - Thank you , son .
Okay , vampire killers , let 's kill some fuckin ' vampires .
[ Roaring , Hissing ]
Those who walk in the darkness have seen the light .
In the darkness have seen the light .
In the darkness , the light .
[ Motor Humming ]
Those who walk in the darkness have seen the light .
Kill ' em all !
[ Vampire Screeching ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gagging , Neck Muscles Cracking ]
- [ Screeching ] - Come on ! Come on !
[ Growling ]
[ Motor Sputtering ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Whistles ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Sighs ]
- Dad ? - [ Growls ]
[ Screaming ] Dad ! No , Dad !
Dad ! Dad !
I swear to God in Jesus Christ 's name .
Oh , my God !
[ Grunting ] Fight now , cry later !
- [ Growling ] - [ Screaming ]
Get the fuck off ! Get off ! Get off ! Get ' em off !
[ Screaming ]
Kill me , Kate .
Just kill me , Kate .
[ Exhales Deeply ] I can 't .
- How many bullets you have ? - I don 't know . Not many .
When you run out , start cold-cockin' 'em . Make ' em sing for their supper .
[ Vampires Growling , Hissing ]
Seth , should I save the last bullets for us ?
No . Use it on the next fuck that tries to bite you .
[ Screeching ]
Shoot more holes . Shoot more holes !
- Come here ! - They can 't go into the light .
Come here . Come here ! All right .
Hey , Seth , don 't leave me .
Come here . Come here . Come on !
- Come on , you ! - [ Screeching ]
- Come here , you fucks ! - [ Gasps ]
- [ Pounding On Door ] - [ Man ] Hello ? I 'm looking for my friend Seth .
Carlos ! Kick in the door !
- [ Gunshot ] - [ Screeching ]
Go !
Son of a bitch .
[ All Screeching ]
[ Grunts ]
What the fuck was goin ' on in there ? [ Groans ]
[ Groaning ]
What 's the matter with you ? Are you crazy ?
Why , out of all the godforsaken shitholes in Mexico , do we have to meet here ?
One place is just as good as another .
You ever been here before ?
[ Chuckles ] No . Ah , I drove by it a couple times .
It 's a rowdy place . It 's out in the middle of nowhere .
There 'll be no cops . And it 's open from dusk ' til dawn .
Didn 't you say you wanted to meet in the morning ? Here we are .
Since you just picked this place out of a hat , my brother is dead ,
that girl 's entire fucking family is dead !
What ? Were they psychos , or- -
They look like psychos ? Is that what they looked like ? They were vampires .
Psychos do not explode when sunlight hits ' em .
I don 't give a fuck how crazy they are !
Seth ... how can I make it up to you ?
You can 't make it up to me , Carlos . You can 't do it .
Can 't make it up !
Fifteen percent instead of 30 % for my stay in El Rey , that 's a good start .
[ Chuckles ] Twenty-eight .
My brother 's gone . You understand that ?
He 's gone and he 's not comin ' back , and that is your fault .
- Twenty . - [ Chuckles ]
[ Together ] Twenty-five .
Kate . Go to the R.V. , get the suitcase .
You look like hell .
You want a cold beer ? I got some in the car .
Come on , they 're cold . Huh ?
I got Mexican and domestic .
Chingalo .
- [ Carlos ] So , how do you like the car ? - It 's all right .
I said " like new . " This is a ' 90 .
Hey , it is new , cabron . Belonged to a drug dealer friend of mine .
Hey , he only drove it like 14 times in five years . It 's like new , I swear to God .
- So , what do I do , follow you ? - Yeah , follow me .
- All right , let 's do it . - [ Chuckling ]
I 'm sorry .
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah , I 'm sorry too .
- I 'll see ya . - Seth ?
You need some company ?
Kate , do you know where I 'm goin ' ? Do you know what El Rey is ?
- No . - [ Carlos ] Hey , Seth .
It 's time to go .
Go home , Kate .
I may be a bastard , but I 'm not a fuckin ' bastard .
[ Engine Starts ]
~ Hot air hangs like a dead man ~
~ From a white oak tree ~
~ People sitting 'on porches ~
~ Thinkin ' how things used to be ~
~ Dark night ~
~ It 's a dark night ~
~ It 's a dark night ~ ~
~ Everything about her was natural ~
~ Everything about her was cool ~
~ But I 'm a little partial for beautiful girls ~
~ Even if their bloods run blue ~
~ I think I see her ~
~ I think I want her ~
~ I think I love her ~
~ She 's just killin ' me ~
~ I think she 's killin ' me ~
~ Her castanets are enormous ~
~ Her bongo beat absolute ~
~ And when she doin midnight performances ~
~ She 's got a secret somethin ' to boot ~
~ I think I see her ~
~ I think I want her ~
~ Oh , I think I love her ~
~ But she 's just killin ' me Killin ' me ~
~ I think she 's killin ' me ~
~ Oooh ~
[ Howling ]
~ Listen Miss Santanica Pandemonia ~
~ Don 't get any lower or slower ~
~ What you see is what you get conmigo ~
~ And the bonus of an albino boa ~
~ I think I see her ~
~ I think I want her ~
~ Yes , I think I love her ~
~ She 's just killin ' me Killin ' me ~
~ She 's just killin ' me That 's some time I had ~
~ Oh , I think I see her ~
~ I know I love her ~
~ Yes , I might love her ~
~ She 's just killin ' me ~
~ She wanna be killin ' me ~
~ Suck my blood ~ ~
[ Laughing ]